set up a meeting with someone that you absolutely trust
be assassinated. I like to drink mine more than
I used to. Anyway, I'm thinking more.
It's good for you, But I don't know your
wife until I'm the happy with them. Very happy
mind the way I keep going over this pass.
an old habit. I spent my life trying not
, but not men. Mhm. How's your boy
like every day. Yeah. You're smarter than I
funny papers. Read the funny papers. Mm hmm
. Uh huh. I want you to arrange to
have a telephone, man, check all the calls
. Good care of that. Oh, that's right
. I forgot. What's the matter? What's bothering
you? I'll handle it. I told you I
can handle it. I'll handle it. I knew
that Santino was going to have to go through all
I was no, and I never I never wanted
this for you. I want my own life.
I don't apologize to take care of my family.
by all those big shots. Mhm. I don't
apologize. That's my life. But I thought that
mhm But when it was your time that the Jew
, Governor Corleone, something another person alive and well
, this wasn't enough time. Michael was enough time
. Mm. Yeah, yeah. Now, listen
, Whoever comes to you with this bars, any